Hello.
こんにちは
Your sister is cute.
お姉さんは可愛いですね
Your skin is white.
白いですね、肌が
yes.
はい
What do you usually do?
普段って何してるんですか?
I usually go to school.
普段は学校を通ってます
Are you a student?
学生さんなんですか?
By the way, what school do you go to?
ちなみに何の学校通ってますか?
Aiming to be an announcer.
アナウンサー目指してて
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなんですか?
Should I aim to be an announcer?
アナウンサー目指していいですか?
That's fine.
いいです
That's amazing.
すごいですね
Do you want to become an announcer in the future?
将来アナウンサーになりたい?
I want to see it.
見たい
But I guess you can do it because you're cute, right?
でも可愛いからなれるんじゃないですか?
No, not at all.
いや、全然そんなことないです
So, there are people you admire.
じゃあ憧れてる人とかいるんですね
Why did you want to become one?
なんでなりたいと思ったんですか?
why?
なんで?
Why?
なんでだろう?
Because I've always admired you.
ずっと憧れてたから
ah.
ああ
Is it okay for this to come out?
これ 出ちゃって大丈夫ですか?
Well, that's right.
まあ、そうです
Do you have a boyfriend now?
今、彼氏いるんですか?
not present?
いない?
How long have you been gone?
どれくらいいないんですか?
About 2 years.
2年くらい
Two years?
2年も?
It's quite long.
結構長いですね
Isn't it quite long?
だいぶ長くないですか?
It's long.
長いです
But you'll be popular, because you're cute.
でもモテるでしょ、可愛いから
No, not at all.
いや、全然
Really not?
本当にない?
That's not true.
そんなことない
That's right.
そうだ
I think you get approached a lot, right?
結構アプローチされるんじゃないですか?
Will it be?
されます?
But you don't want to date?
でも付き合う気はないんですか?
No.
ないです
why?
なぜ?
busy.
忙しい
I'm changing schools.
学校変えてるもんね
Are dreams really more important?
やっぱり夢の方が大事なんですか?
In order to achieve my dreams, I have to let go of that kind of love.
夢のためにはそういう恋愛も捨てていかないと
What kind of men do you like?
どういう男性が好きですか?
What do you mean...
どういう...
A manly person.
男 っぽい人
A manly person?
男 っぽい人?
wonderful person.
素晴らしい人
What is your personality?
性格が?
Personality.
性格が
For example, what kind?
例えばどんな?
No matter what, there are people who don't worry too much.
どんな、あんま悩ん悩んしてない人がいる
It's like he's taking the lead.
リードしてくれるみたいな
Were you always like that?
元からもそういう人だったんですか?
Yeah.
うん
Oh, no.
あ、違う
Why did you break up?
なんで別れちゃったんですか?
It looked a bit like a girl.
ちょっとね、女の子っぽかった
It's quite troublesome.
結構、めんどくさい
That's why I started hating it.
だから 嫌いになっちゃったんですね
Have you been worrying and worrying?
悩ん悩んしてた?
Is your grandfather S or M?
おじいさんはSかMかってどっちですか?
M...maybe?
M...かな?
Is it better to be attacked?
攻められる方がいい?
Do you have an erogenous body?
性感体ありますか?
I don't know.
わかんない
There's no such thing as not knowing.
わかんないってことないんでしょ
Do you have sex alone?
一人でエッチします?
I don't.
しないです
do not?
しない?
Isn't that a lie?
嘘でしょ?
do not.
しない
Not even once?
一回も?
Yes, but is there anything I should do?
あるけど、 しなことはある?
Yes, but I don't.
あるけど、しない
For two years, two years without a boyfriend,
2年間の間、彼氏がいない2年間の間、
Did you not have sex at all?
全くセックスしなかったんですか?
Did you have that kind of romance?
そういうロマンスあったんですか?
Well, by the way, who did you meet?
まあ、 ち なみに誰と会ったんですか?
It's my ex-boyfriend.
元彼です
Is that your ex-boyfriend?
元彼かい?
Did you have sex with your ex?
元彼とセックスしてたんですか?
I knew.
知ってました
You hated it, right?
嫌いだったんでしょ?
That's right.
それは、そう
Why did you decide to have sex?
なんでセックスすることになったんですか?
Because I was forced to do so, I was reluctant to be generous.
迫られたから、 惜しみ弱い
Does it mean that you are not generous?
惜しみ弱いって意味なんですか?
I guess my ex-boyfriend just kept going.
元彼にグイグイ行かれちゃったんですね
I see.
なるほど
got it.
わかりました
Well then, let's do all the embarrassing things that your sister does.
じゃあ、そんな お姉さんの 恥ずかしいことをいっぱい しちゃ
Is that okay?
って いいですか?
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Are you nervous?
緊張してる?
I have to get used to having the camera pointed at me.
もう、カメラ向けられるの 慣れなきゃ
Not used to it?
慣れてない?
I'm not used to it.
慣れてない
It's going to be directed at you from now on, right?
これから向けられていくんでしょ、
full.
いっぱい
Have you had a good time recently?
最近イチイチしたの?
recently?
最近?
Since when?
いつから?
How many months ago?
何ヶ月か前?
copper?
どう?
What do you like?
どうって何がいいんですか?
What do you think about having a dick for the first time in a while?
久しぶりにチンチンしたって、どう?
Huh?
えっ?
What do you think?
感想は?
I don't know.
分かんない
Don't you understand?
分かんない?
what up?
どうした?
Big boobs.
大きいね、おっぱい
It's so soft.
すっごい柔らかい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
a bit.
少し
Try thinning your eyes.
目に痩せてみて
Long live it.
万歳してくれ
I like the style.
スタイルいいね
Stick your butt out.
お尻突き出してくれ
Face your butt.
お尻向いて
Get your hands on it.
手ついて
Stick your butt out.
お尻突き出してくれ
Look this way.
こっち向いて
It's kind of damp.
なんか湿ってるね
Yeah.
うん
Why is it so damp?
なんでこんなに湿ってるの?
Show me your beautiful breasts.
綺麗なおっぱい見せてよ
Show me properly.
ちゃんと見せて
It's damp.
湿ってる
Take off your pants.
パンツ抜いて
Open your legs.
足開いて
Open your pussy with your own hands.
自分の手で まんこ開いて
With both hands.
両手で
Put your hand through it from the inside.
手をさ、 内側から通して
Why is it so damp?
なんでこんなに湿ってるの?
Which do you prefer, inside or outside?
中と外、どっちが好き?
Look at me for a second.
こっち見て、ちょっと
Look here.
こ っち見て
There's a lot of noise.
こよぐしょいってる
Spread your legs properly.
足開いて、ちゃんと
copper?
どう?
Touch it yourself.
自分のまま触ってね
It's bad, it's bad, it's bad.
やばい、やばい、やばい
terrible.
やばい
Oh no, no no.
やばい、やばい
It's out.
出ちゃった
Did you come out for a while?
ちょっと出た?
I didn't say that.
なんて言ってない
terrible.
やばい
I exploded.
暴発しちゃった
It's really dripping.
すげえ垂れてる
Sorry.
ごめんね
What does it taste like?
どんな味する?
Yeah.
うん
Bitter?
苦 い?
bitter?
苦い?
Just a moment while looking up.
上見ながらちょっと
It feels so good.
すっげえ気持ちいいね
Take it off.
手外して
Lick the ground.
地首舐めて
Touch my dick with your left hand.
左手でチンチン触って
Put your dick between her big tits.
大きなおっぱいにさ、 チンチン挟んで
Um...
えっと...
yes.
そう
terrible.
やばい
Because it's going up to your knees, your knees.
膝、膝の上に上がっていくから
Playing with chin chin.
チンチン遊んで
yes.
そう
played
遊んだ
Isn't that true?
こと ない?
do not have.
ない
No.
ないです
It may appear in the announcement exam.
アナウンス試験で出てるかもしれない
It's going to get crunchy on the ground,
地首にさ、 コリコリしていくからよ、
Ching Chin.
チンチン
good?
いい?
Yeah.
うん
Do it yourself?
自分でやって?
Doing dicks on the ground?
地首にチンチンやってる?
Yeah.
うん
Can I see it?
見えていい?
Why don't you just climb on top?
そのまま、 上に乗ってごらん?
Why don't you move slowly?
ゆっくり動いてごらん?
Why don't you try moving yourself?
自分で動いてごらん?